<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
	<channel>
		<title><![CDATA[Ulysses Audiobook]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Ulysses is a modernist novel by Irish writer James Joyce. It was first serialised in parts in the American journal The Little Review from March 1918 to December 1920, and then published in its entirety by Sylvia Beach in February 1922, in Paris. It is considered to be one of the most important works of modernist literature, and has been called "a demonstration and summation of the entire movement". According to Declan Kiberd, "Before Joyce, no writer of fiction had so foregrounded the process of thinking."]]></description>
		<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
		<image>
            <url>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg</url>
			<title>Ulysses Audiobook</title>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
		</image>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 02:43:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<author>Cyper</author>
		<copyright>Cyper</copyright>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<itunes:author>Cyper</itunes:author>
		<itunes:summary>Cyper&apos;s Deployment Program</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
		<itunes:owner>
			<itunes:name>Cyper</itunes:name>
			<itunes:email>richardtrinh12@gmail.com</itunes:email>
		</itunes:owner>
		<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
		<itunes:category text="Books"/>
		<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
        
		<item>
			<title>Telemachus</title>
			<description>Stately, plump Buck Mulligan came from the stairhead, bearing a bowl of lather on which a mirror and a razor lay crossed. A yellow dressinggown, ungirdled, was sustained gently behind him by the mild morning air. He held the bowl aloft and intoned: — Introibo ad altare Dei.</description>
            <itunes:order>1</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/01%20Telemachus.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 12:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/01%20Telemachus.mp3" length="23282770" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Stately, plump Buck Mulligan came from the stairhead, bearing a bowl of lather on which a mirror and a razor lay crossed. A yellow dressinggown, ungirdled, was sustained gently behind him by the mild morning air. He held the bowl aloft and intoned: — Introibo ad altare Dei.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Nestor</title>
			<description>The cock crew, / The sky was blue: / The bells in heaven / Were striking eleven. / 'Tis time for this poor soul / To go to heaven.</description>
            <itunes:order>2</itunes:order>

			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/02%20Nestor.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 13:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/02%20Nestor.mp3" length="16216186" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>The cock crew, / The sky was blue: / The bells in heaven / Were striking eleven. / 'Tis time for this poor soul / To go to heaven.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Proteus</title>
			<description>Ineluctable modality of the visible: at least that if no more, thought through my eyes. Signatures of all things I am here to read, seaspawn and seawrack, the nearing tide, that rusty boot. Snotgreen, bluesilver, rust: coloured signs. Limits of the diaphane. But he adds: in bodies. Then he was aware of them bodies before of them coloured. How? By knocking his sconce against them, sure. Go easy. Bald he was and a millionaire, maestro di color che sanno. Limit of the diaphane in. Why in? Diaphane, adiaphane. If you can put your five fingers through it it is a gate, if not a door. Shut your eyes and see.</description>
            <itunes:order>3</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/03%20Proteus.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 14:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/03%20Proteus.mp3" length="23746768" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Ineluctable modality of the visible: at least that if no more, thought through my eyes. Signatures of all things I am here to read, seaspawn and seawrack, the nearing tide, that rusty boot. Snotgreen, bluesilver, rust: coloured signs. Limits of the diaphane. But he adds: in bodies. Then he was aware of them bodies before of them coloured. How? By knocking his sconce against them, sure. Go easy. Bald he was and a millionaire, maestro di color che sanno. Limit of the diaphane in. Why in? Diaphane, adiaphane. If you can put your five fingers through it it is a gate, if not a door. Shut your eyes and see.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Calypso</title>
			<description>Grey horror seared his flesh. Folding the page into his pocket he turned into Eccles street, hurrying homeward. Cold oils slid along his veins, chilling his blood: age crusting him with a salt cloak. Well, I am here now. Morning mouth bad images. Got up wrong side of the bed. Must begin again those Sandow's exercises. On the hands down. Blotchy brown brick houses. Number eighty still unlet. Why is that? Valuation is only twenty-eight. Towers, Battersby, North, MacArthur: parlour windows plastered with bills. Plasters on a sore eye. To smell the gentle smoke of tea, fume of the pan, sizzling butter. Be near her ample bedwarmed flesh. Yes, yes.</description>
            <itunes:order>4</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/04%20Calypso.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 15:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/04%20Calypso.mp3" length="22601351" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Grey horror seared his flesh. Folding the page into his pocket he turned into Eccles street, hurrying homeward. Cold oils slid along his veins, chilling his blood: age crusting him with a salt cloak. Well, I am here now. Morning mouth bad images. Got up wrong side of the bed. Must begin again those Sandow's exercises. On the hands down. Blotchy brown brick houses. Number eighty still unlet. Why is that? Valuation is only twenty-eight. Towers, Battersby, North, MacArthur: parlour windows plastered with bills. Plasters on a sore eye. To smell the gentle smoke of tea, fume of the pan, sizzling butter. Be near her ample bedwarmed flesh. Yes, yes.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Lotus Eaters</title>
			<description>Something going on: some sodality. Pity so empty. Nice discreet place to be next some girl. Who is my neighbour? Jammed by the hour to slow music. That woman at midnight mass. Seventh heaven. Women knelt in the benches with crimson halters round their necks, heads bowed. A batch knelt at the altarrails. The priest went along by them, murmuring, holding the thing in his hands. He stopped at each, took out a communion, shook a drop or two (are they in water?) off it and put it neatly into her mouth. Her hat and head sank. Then the next one: a small old woman. The priest bent down to put it into her mouth, murmuring all the time. Latin. The next one. Shut your eyes and open your mouth. What? Corpus: body. Corpse. Good idea the Latin. Stupefies them first. Hospice for the dying. They don't seem to chew it: only swallow it down. Rum idea: eating bits of a corpse why the cannibals cotton to it.</description>
            <itunes:order>5</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/05%20Lotus%20Eaters.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 16:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/05%20Lotus%20Eaters.mp3" length="21012698" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Something going on: some sodality. Pity so empty. Nice discreet place to be next some girl. Who is my neighbour? Jammed by the hour to slow music. That woman at midnight mass. Seventh heaven. Women knelt in the benches with crimson halters round their necks, heads bowed. A batch knelt at the altarrails. The priest went along by them, murmuring, holding the thing in his hands. He stopped at each, took out a communion, shook a drop or two (are they in water?) off it and put it neatly into her mouth. Her hat and head sank. Then the next one: a small old woman. The priest bent down to put it into her mouth, murmuring all the time. Latin. The next one. Shut your eyes and open your mouth. What? Corpus: body. Corpse. Good idea the Latin. Stupefies them first. Hospice for the dying. They don't seem to chew it: only swallow it down. Rum idea: eating bits of a corpse why the cannibals cotton to it.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hades</title>
			<description>They looked. Murderer's ground. It passed darkly. Shuttered, tenantless, unweeded garden. Whole place gone to hell. Wrongfully condemned. Murder. The murderer's image in the eye of the murdered. They love reading about it. Man's head found in a garden. Her clothing consisted of. How she met her death. Recent outrage. The weapon used. Murderer is still at large. Clues. A shoelace. The body to be exhumed. Murder will out.
Cramped in this carriage. She mightn't like me to come that way without letting her know. Must be careful about women. Catch them once with their pants down. Never forgive you after. Fifteen.
The high railings of Prospect rippled past their gaze. Dark poplars, rare white forms. Forms more frequent, white shapes thronged amid the trees, white forms and fragments streaming by mutely, sustaining vain gestures on the air.
The felly harshed against the curbstone: stopped. Martin Cunningham put out his arm and, wrenching back the handle, shoved the door open with his knee. He stepped out. Mr Power and Mr Dedalus followed.
Change that soap now. Mr Bloom's hand unbuttoned his hip pocket swiftly and transferred the paperstuck soap to his inner handkerchief pocket. He stepped out of the carriage, replacing the newspaper his other hand still held.
Paltry funeral: coach and three carriages. It's all the same. Pallbearers, gold reins, requiem mass, firing a volley. Pomp of death. Beyond the hind carriage a hawker stood by his barrow of cakes and fruit. Simnel cakes those are, stuck together: cakes for the dead. Dogbiscuits. Who ate them? Mourners coming out.
He followed his companions. Mr Kernan and Ned Lambert followed, Hynes walking after them. Corny Kelleher stood by the opened hearse and took out the two wreaths. He handed one to the boy.
Where is that child's funeral disappeared to?
A team of horses passed from Finglas with toiling plodding tread, dragging through the funereal silence a creaking waggon on which lay a granite block. The waggoner marching at their head saluted.
Coffin now. Got here before us, dead as he is. Horse looking round at it with his plume skeowways. Dull eye: collar tight on his neck, pressing on a bloodvessel or something. Do they know what they cart out here every day? Must be twenty or thirty funerals every day. Then Mount Jerome for the protestants. Funerals all over the world everywhere every minute. Shovelling them under by the cartload doublequick. Thousands every hour. Too many in the world.
Mourners came out through the gates: woman and a girl. Leanjawed harpy, hard woman at a bargain, her bonnet awry. Girl's face stained with dirt and tears, holding the woman's arm, looking up at her for a sign to cry. Fish's face, bloodless and livid.
The mutes shouldered the coffin and bore it in through the gates. So much dead weight. Felt heavier myself stepping out of that bath. First the stiff: then the friends of the stiff. Corny Kelleher and the boy followed with their wreaths. Who is that beside them? Ah, the brother-in-law.</description>
            <itunes:order>6</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/06%20Hades.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 17:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/06%20Hades.mp3" length="33752080" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>They looked. Murderer's ground. It passed darkly. Shuttered, tenantless, unweeded garden. Whole place gone to hell. Wrongfully condemned. Murder. The murderer's image in the eye of the murdered. They love reading about it. Man's head found in a garden. Her clothing consisted of. How she met her death. Recent outrage. The weapon used. Murderer is still at large. Clues. A shoelace. The body to be exhumed. Murder will out.
Cramped in this carriage. She mightn't like me to come that way without letting her know. Must be careful about women. Catch them once with their pants down. Never forgive you after. Fifteen.
The high railings of Prospect rippled past their gaze. Dark poplars, rare white forms. Forms more frequent, white shapes thronged amid the trees, white forms and fragments streaming by mutely, sustaining vain gestures on the air.
The felly harshed against the curbstone: stopped. Martin Cunningham put out his arm and, wrenching back the handle, shoved the door open with his knee. He stepped out. Mr Power and Mr Dedalus followed.
Change that soap now. Mr Bloom's hand unbuttoned his hip pocket swiftly and transferred the paperstuck soap to his inner handkerchief pocket. He stepped out of the carriage, replacing the newspaper his other hand still held.
Paltry funeral: coach and three carriages. It's all the same. Pallbearers, gold reins, requiem mass, firing a volley. Pomp of death. Beyond the hind carriage a hawker stood by his barrow of cakes and fruit. Simnel cakes those are, stuck together: cakes for the dead. Dogbiscuits. Who ate them? Mourners coming out.
He followed his companions. Mr Kernan and Ned Lambert followed, Hynes walking after them. Corny Kelleher stood by the opened hearse and took out the two wreaths. He handed one to the boy.
Where is that child's funeral disappeared to?
A team of horses passed from Finglas with toiling plodding tread, dragging through the funereal silence a creaking waggon on which lay a granite block. The waggoner marching at their head saluted.
Coffin now. Got here before us, dead as he is. Horse looking round at it with his plume skeowways. Dull eye: collar tight on his neck, pressing on a bloodvessel or something. Do they know what they cart out here every day? Must be twenty or thirty funerals every day. Then Mount Jerome for the protestants. Funerals all over the world everywhere every minute. Shovelling them under by the cartload doublequick. Thousands every hour. Too many in the world.
Mourners came out through the gates: woman and a girl. Leanjawed harpy, hard woman at a bargain, her bonnet awry. Girl's face stained with dirt and tears, holding the woman's arm, looking up at her for a sign to cry. Fish's face, bloodless and livid.
The mutes shouldered the coffin and bore it in through the gates. So much dead weight. Felt heavier myself stepping out of that bath. First the stiff: then the friends of the stiff. Corny Kelleher and the boy followed with their wreaths. Who is that beside them? Ah, the brother-in-law.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Aeolus</title>
			<description>IN THE HEART OF THE HIBERNIAN METROPOLIS</description>
            <itunes:order>7</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/07%20Aeolus.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 18:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/07%20Aeolus.mp3" length="33282505" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>IN THE HEART OF THE HIBERNIAN METROPOLIS</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Lestrygonians</title>
			<description>A procession of whitesmocked men marched slowly towards him along the gutter, scarlet sashes across their boards. Bargains. Like that priest they are this morning: we have sinned: we have suffered. He read the scarlet letters on their five tall white hats: H. E. L. Y. S. Wisdom Hely's. Y lagging behind drew a chunk of bread from under his foreboard, crammed it into his mouth and munched as he walked. Our staple food. Three bob a day, walking along the gutters, street after street. Just keep skin and bone together, bread and skilly. They are not Boyl: no, M'Glade's men. Doesn't bring in any business either. I suggested to him about a transparent showcart with two smart girls sitting inside writing letters, copybooks, envelopes, blottingpaper. I bet that would have caught on. Smart girls writing something catch the eye at once. Everyone dying to know what she's writing. Get twenty of them round you if you stare at nothing. Have a finger in the pie. Women too. Curiosity. Pillar of salt. Wouldn't have it of course because he didn't think of it himself first. Or the inkbottle I suggested with a false stain of black celluloid. His ideas for ads like Plumtree's potted under the obituaries, cold meat department. You can't lick 'em. What? Our envelopes. Hello, Jones, where are you going? Can't stop, Robinson, I am hastening to purchase the only reliable inkeraser Kansell, sold by Hely's Ltd, 85 Dame street. Well out of that ruck I am. Devil of a job it was collecting accounts of those convents. Tranquilla convent. That was a nice nun there, really sweet face. Wimple suited her small head. Sister? Sister? I am sure she was crossed in love by her eyes. Very hard to bargain with that sort of woman. I disturbed her at her devotions that morning. But glad to communicate with the outside world. Our great day, she said. Feast of Our Lady of Mount Carmel. Sweet name too: caramel. She knew, I think she knew by the way she. If she had married she would have changed. I suppose they really were short of money. Fried everything in the best butter all the same. No lard for them. My heart's broke eating dripping. They like buttering themselves in and out. Molly tasting it, her veil up. Sister? Pat Claffey, the pawnbroker's daughter. It was a nun they say invented barbed wire.</description>
            <itunes:order>8</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/08%20Lestrygonians.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 19:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/08%20Lestrygonians.mp3" length="40896927" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>A procession of whitesmocked men marched slowly towards him along the gutter, scarlet sashes across their boards. Bargains. Like that priest they are this morning: we have sinned: we have suffered. He read the scarlet letters on their five tall white hats: H. E. L. Y. S. Wisdom Hely's. Y lagging behind drew a chunk of bread from under his foreboard, crammed it into his mouth and munched as he walked. Our staple food. Three bob a day, walking along the gutters, street after street. Just keep skin and bone together, bread and skilly. They are not Boyl: no, M'Glade's men. Doesn't bring in any business either. I suggested to him about a transparent showcart with two smart girls sitting inside writing letters, copybooks, envelopes, blottingpaper. I bet that would have caught on. Smart girls writing something catch the eye at once. Everyone dying to know what she's writing. Get twenty of them round you if you stare at nothing. Have a finger in the pie. Women too. Curiosity. Pillar of salt. Wouldn't have it of course because he didn't think of it himself first. Or the inkbottle I suggested with a false stain of black celluloid. His ideas for ads like Plumtree's potted under the obituaries, cold meat department. You can't lick 'em. What? Our envelopes. Hello, Jones, where are you going? Can't stop, Robinson, I am hastening to purchase the only reliable inkeraser Kansell, sold by Hely's Ltd, 85 Dame street. Well out of that ruck I am. Devil of a job it was collecting accounts of those convents. Tranquilla convent. That was a nice nun there, really sweet face. Wimple suited her small head. Sister? Sister? I am sure she was crossed in love by her eyes. Very hard to bargain with that sort of woman. I disturbed her at her devotions that morning. But glad to communicate with the outside world. Our great day, she said. Feast of Our Lady of Mount Carmel. Sweet name too: caramel. She knew, I think she knew by the way she. If she had married she would have changed. I suppose they really were short of money. Fried everything in the best butter all the same. No lard for them. My heart's broke eating dripping. They like buttering themselves in and out. Molly tasting it, her veil up. Sister? Pat Claffey, the pawnbroker's daughter. It was a nun they say invented barbed wire.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Scylla And Charybdis</title>
			<description> — Is it possible that that player Shakespeare, a ghost by absence, and in the vesture of buried Denmark, a ghost by death, speaking his own words to his own son's name (had Hamnet Shakespeare lived he would have been prince Hamlet's twin), is it possible, I want to know, or probable that he did not draw or foresee the logical conclusion of those premises: you are the dispossessed son: I am the murdered father: your mother is the guilty queen, Ann Shakespeare, born Hathaway?</description>
            <itunes:order>9</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/09%20Scylla%20And%20Charybdis.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 20:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/09%20Scylla%20And%20Charybdis.mp3" length="37331749 " type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary> — Is it possible that that player Shakespeare, a ghost by absence, and in the vesture of buried Denmark, a ghost by death, speaking his own words to his own son's name (had Hamnet Shakespeare lived he would have been prince Hamlet's twin), is it possible, I want to know, or probable that he did not draw or foresee the logical conclusion of those premises: you are the dispossessed son: I am the murdered father: your mother is the guilty queen, Ann Shakespeare, born Hathaway?</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Wandering Rocks</title>
			<description>Damn good gin that was. </description>
            <itunes:order>10</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/10%20Wandering%20Rocks.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 21:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/10%20Wandering%20Rocks.mp3" length="41561695" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Damn good gin that was.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sirens</title>
			<description>Imperthnthn thnthnthn</description>
            <itunes:order>11</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/11%20Sirens.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 22:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/11%20Sirens.mp3" length="47300257" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Imperthnthn thnthnthn</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cyclops</title>
			<description>I was just passing the time of day with old Troy of the D. M. P. at the corner of Arbour hill there and be damned but a bloody sweep came along and he near drove his gear into my eye. I turned around to let him have the weight of my tongue when who should I see dodging along Stony Batter only Joe Hynes.</description>
            <itunes:order>12</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/12%20Cyclops.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 23:41:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/12%20Cyclops.mp3" length="64631772" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>I was just passing the time of day with old Troy of the D. M. P. at the corner of Arbour hill there and be damned but a bloody sweep came along and he near drove his gear into my eye. I turned around to let him have the weight of my tongue when who should I see dodging along Stony Batter only Joe Hynes.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Nausica</title>
			<description>The twins were now playing again right merrily for the troubles of childhood are but as fleeting summer showers. Cissy played with baby Boardman till he crowed with glee, clapping baby hands in air. Peep she cried behind the hood of the pushcar and Edy asked where was Cissy gone and then Cissy popped up her head and cried ah! and, my word, didn't the little chap enjoy that! And then she told him to say papa.</description>
            <itunes:order>13</itunes:order>
			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/13%20Nausica.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 23:46:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/13%20Nausica.mp3" length="50470897" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>The twins were now playing again right merrily for the troubles of childhood are but as fleeting summer showers. Cissy played with baby Boardman till he crowed with glee, clapping baby hands in air. Peep she cried behind the hood of the pushcar and Edy asked where was Cissy gone and then Cissy popped up her head and cried ah! and, my word, didn't the little chap enjoy that! And then she told him to say papa.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Oxen and the Sun</title>
			<description>For they were right witty scholars. And he heard their aresouns each gen other as touching birth and righteousness, young Madden maintaining that put such case it were hard the wife to die (for so it had fallen out a matter of some year agone with a woman of Eblana in Horne's house that now was trespassed out of this world and the self night next before her death all leeches and pothecaries had taken counsel of her case). And they said farther she should live because in the beginning, they said, the woman should bring forth in pain and wherefore they that were of this imagination affirmed how young Madden had said truth for he had conscience to let her die. And not few and of these was young Lynch were in doubt that the world was now right evil governed as it was never other howbeit the mean people believed it otherwise but the law nor his judges did provide no remedy. A redress God grant. This was scant said but all cried with one acclaim nay, by our Virgin Mother, the wife should live and the babe to die. In colour whereof they waxed hot upon that head what with argument and what for their drinking but the franklin Lenehan was prompt each when to pour them ale so that at the least way mirth might not lack. Then young Madden showed all the whole affair and when he said how that she was dead and how for holy religion sake by rede of palmer and bedesman and for a vow he had made to Saint Ultan of Arbraccan her goodman husband would not let her death whereby they were all wondrous grieved. To whom young Stephen had these words following: Murmur, sirs, is eke oft among lay folk. Both babe and parent now glorify their Maker, the one in limbo gloom, the other in purgefire. But, gramercy, what of those Godpossibled souls that we nightly impossibilise, which is the sin against the Holy Ghost, Very God, Lord and Giver of Life? For, sirs, he said, our lust is brief. We are means to those small creatures within us and nature has other ends than we. Then said Dixon junior to Punch Costello wist he what ends. But he had overmuch drunken and the best word he could have of him was that he would ever dishonest a woman whoso she were or wife or maid or leman if it so fortuned him to be delivered of his spleen of lustihead. Whereat Crotthers of Alba Longa sang young Malachi's praise of that beast the unicorn how once in the millennium he cometh by his horn, the other all this while, pricked forward with their jibes wherewith they did malice him, witnessing all and several by saint Foutinus his engines that he was able to do any manner of thing that lay in man to do. Thereat laughed they all right jocundly only young Stephen and sir Leopold which never durst laugh too open by reason of a strange humour which he would not bewray and also for that he rued for her that bare whoso she might be or wheresoever. Then spoke young Stephen orgulous of mother Church that would cast him out of her bosom, of law of canons, of Lilith, patron of abortions, of bigness wrought by wind of seeds of brightness or by potency of vampires mouth to mouth or, as Virgilius saith, by the influence of the occident or by the reek of moonflower or an she lie with a woman which her man has but lain with, effectu secuto, or peradventure in her bath according to the opinions of Averroes and Moses Maimonides. He said also how at the end of the second month a human soul was infused and how in all our holy mother foldeth ever souls for God's greater glory whereas that earthly mother which was but a dam to bring forth beastly should die by canon for so saith he that holdeth the fisherman's seal, even that blessed Peter on which rock was holy church for all ages founded. All they bachelors then asked of sir Leopold would he in like case so jeopard her person as risk life to save life. A wariness of mind he would answer as fitted all and, laying hand to jaw, he said dissembling, as his wont was, that as it was informed him, who had ever loved the art of physic as might a layman, and agreeing also with his experience of so seldom seen an accident it was good for that mother Church belike at one blow had birth and death pence and in such sort deliverly he scaped their questions. That is truth, pardy, said Dixon, and, or I err, a pregnant word. Which hearing young Stephen was a marvellous glad man and he averred that he who stealeth from the poor lendeth to the Lord for he was of a wild manner when he was drunken and that he was now in that taking it appeared eftsoons.</description>
			<itunes:order>14</itunes:order>

			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/14%20Oxen%20Of%20The%20Sun.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 23:50:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/14%20Oxen%20Of%20The%20Sun.mp3" length="68055738" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>For they were right witty scholars. And he heard their aresouns each gen other as touching birth and righteousness, young Madden maintaining that put such case it were hard the wife to die (for so it had fallen out a matter of some year agone with a woman of Eblana in Horne's house that now was trespassed out of this world and the self night next before her death all leeches and pothecaries had taken counsel of her case). And they said farther she should live because in the beginning, they said, the woman should bring forth in pain and wherefore they that were of this imagination affirmed how young Madden had said truth for he had conscience to let her die. And not few and of these was young Lynch were in doubt that the world was now right evil governed as it was never other howbeit the mean people believed it otherwise but the law nor his judges did provide no remedy. A redress God grant. This was scant said but all cried with one acclaim nay, by our Virgin Mother, the wife should live and the babe to die. In colour whereof they waxed hot upon that head what with argument and what for their drinking but the franklin Lenehan was prompt each when to pour them ale so that at the least way mirth might not lack. Then young Madden showed all the whole affair and when he said how that she was dead and how for holy religion sake by rede of palmer and bedesman and for a vow he had made to Saint Ultan of Arbraccan her goodman husband would not let her death whereby they were all wondrous grieved. To whom young Stephen had these words following: Murmur, sirs, is eke oft among lay folk. Both babe and parent now glorify their Maker, the one in limbo gloom, the other in purgefire. But, gramercy, what of those Godpossibled souls that we nightly impossibilise, which is the sin against the Holy Ghost, Very God, Lord and Giver of Life? For, sirs, he said, our lust is brief. We are means to those small creatures within us and nature has other ends than we. Then said Dixon junior to Punch Costello wist he what ends. But he had overmuch drunken and the best word he could have of him was that he would ever dishonest a woman whoso she were or wife or maid or leman if it so fortuned him to be delivered of his spleen of lustihead. Whereat Crotthers of Alba Longa sang young Malachi's praise of that beast the unicorn how once in the millennium he cometh by his horn, the other all this while, pricked forward with their jibes wherewith they did malice him, witnessing all and several by saint Foutinus his engines that he was able to do any manner of thing that lay in man to do. Thereat laughed they all right jocundly only young Stephen and sir Leopold which never durst laugh too open by reason of a strange humour which he would not bewray and also for that he rued for her that bare whoso she might be or wheresoever. Then spoke young Stephen orgulous of mother Church that would cast him out of her bosom, of law of canons, of Lilith, patron of abortions, of bigness wrought by wind of seeds of brightness or by potency of vampires mouth to mouth or, as Virgilius saith, by the influence of the occident or by the reek of moonflower or an she lie with a woman which her man has but lain with, effectu secuto, or peradventure in her bath according to the opinions of Averroes and Moses Maimonides. He said also how at the end of the second month a human soul was infused and how in all our holy mother foldeth ever souls for God's greater glory whereas that earthly mother which was but a dam to bring forth beastly should die by canon for so saith he that holdeth the fisherman's seal, even that blessed Peter on which rock was holy church for all ages founded. All they bachelors then asked of sir Leopold would he in like case so jeopard her person as risk life to save life. A wariness of mind he would answer as fitted all and, laying hand to jaw, he said dissembling, as his wont was, that as it was informed him, who had ever loved the art of physic as might a layman, and agreeing also with his experience of so seldom seen an accident it was good for that mother Church belike at one blow had birth and death pence and in such sort deliverly he scaped their questions. That is truth, pardy, said Dixon, and, or I err, a pregnant word. Which hearing young Stephen was a marvellous glad man and he averred that he who stealeth from the poor lendeth to the Lord for he was of a wild manner when he was drunken and that he was now in that taking it appeared eftsoons.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
        <item>
			<title>Circe</title>
			<description>THE GONG: Bang Bang Bla Bak Blud Bugg Bloo.</description>
            <itunes:order>15</itunes:order>

			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/15%20Circe.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 23:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/15%20Circe.mp3" length="64390401" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>THE GONG: Bang Bang Bla Bak Blud Bugg Bloo.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Eumaeus</title>
			<description> — Needs, Mr Bloom ejaculated, professing not the least surprise at the intelligence, I can quite credit the assertion and I guarantee he invariably does. Everyone according to his needs or everyone according to his deeds. But, talking about things in general, where, added he with a smile, will you sleep yourself? Walking to Sandycove is out of the question. And even supposing you did you won't get in after what occurred at Westland Row station. Simply fag out there for nothing. I don't mean to presume to dictate to you in the slightest degree but why did you leave your father's house?</description>
            <itunes:order>16</itunes:order>

			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/16%20Eumaeus.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 1904 23:57:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/16%20Eumaeus.mp3" length="64390401" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary> — Needs, Mr Bloom ejaculated, professing not the least surprise at the intelligence, I can quite credit the assertion and I guarantee he invariably does. Everyone according to his needs or everyone according to his deeds. But, talking about things in general, where, added he with a smile, will you sleep yourself? Walking to Sandycove is out of the question. And even supposing you did you won't get in after what occurred at Westland Row station. Simply fag out there for nothing. I don't mean to presume to dictate to you in the slightest degree but why did you leave your father's house?</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ithaca</title>
			<description>Little Harry Hughes and his schoolfellows all / Went out for to play ball. / And the very first ball little Harry Hughes played / He drove it o'er the jew's garden wall. / And the very second ball little Harry Hughes played / He broke the jew's windows all.</description>
            <itunes:order>17</itunes:order>

			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/17%20Ithaca.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 1904 02:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/17%20Ithaca.mp3" length="75744288" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Little Harry Hughes and his schoolfellows all / Went out for to play ball. / And the very first ball little Harry Hughes played / He drove it o'er the jew's garden wall. / And the very second ball little Harry Hughes played / He broke the jew's windows all.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Penelope</title>
			<description>Yes because he never did a thing like that before as ask to get his breakfast in bed with a couple of eggs since the City Arms hotel when he used to be pretending to be laid up with a sick voice doing his highness to make himself interesting for that old faggot Mrs Riordan that he thought he had a great leg of and she never left us a farthing all for masses for herself and her soul greatest miser ever was actually afraid to lay out 4d for her methylated spirit telling me all her ailments she had too much old chat in her about politics and earthquakes and the end of the world</description>
            <itunes:order>18</itunes:order>

			<link>https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses.html</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/18%20Penelope.mp3</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 1904 02:40:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/18%20Penelope.mp3" length="75744288" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<itunes:summary>Yes because he never did a thing like that before as ask to get his breakfast in bed with a couple of eggs since the City Arms hotel when he used to be pretending to be laid up with a sick voice doing his highness to make himself interesting for that old faggot Mrs Riordan that he thought he had a great leg of and she never left us a farthing all for masses for herself and her soul greatest miser ever was actually afraid to lay out 4d for her methylated spirit telling me all her ailments she had too much old chat in her about politics and earthquakes and the end of the world</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
			<itunes:image href="https://cyperrt.github.io/Deployment-Center/Ulysses/Ulysses.jpg"/>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>